A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Director's correspondence and subject files, 1920-1992., Extent: 45.15 cubic feet (129 boxes). (Box 1-129)
  - Public Library Consultant Reports, 1979-1987.
    - Quarterly reports, 1986 Apr-June. (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Quarterly reports, 1986 July-Sept. (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Quarterly reports, 1986 Oct-Dec. (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Quarterly reports, 1987 Jan-Mar. (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Quarterly reports, 1987 Apr-June. (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Public Library Consultant files, 1972-1986.
    This sub-series consists of 5 boxes and is arranged by topic. The consultant files contain District/Area files, general files, and files for specific consultants. Includes correspondence between the Library Development Director and public library consultants, courtesy copies of consultant's correspondence with public libraries, library boards, local officials (planning district commissioners, city/county administrators, school superintendents, etc.); consultant meeting notes to file; and reports. Topics may include automation, budgets, building needs, conferences, new library service, policies, procedures, regional library systems, standards, statistics, state/federal aid and workshops.
    - Planning District 1 (Area I), 1973-1980. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Planning District 2 (Area I), 1972-1978. (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Planning District 3 (Area I), 19. (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Planning District 4 (Area I), 1972-1982. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Planning District 5 (Area I), 1972-1979. (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Planning District 6 (Area IV), 1972-1981. (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Planning District 7 (Area IV), 1972-1980. (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Planning District 8 (Area IV), 1972-1985. (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Planning District 9 (Area IV), 1972-1977. (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Planning District 10 (Area IV), 1972-1977. (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Planning District 11 (Area II), 1973-1986. (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Planning District 12 (Area II), 1974. (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Planning District 13 (Area II), 1973-1983. (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Planning District 14 (Area II), 1973-1979. (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Planning District 15 (Area III), 1972-1973. (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Planning District 16 (Area III), 1971-1973. (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Planning District 17 (Area III), 1971-1973. (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Planning District 18 (Area III), 1972-1973. (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Planning District 19 (Area III), 1972-1973. (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Planning District 20 (Area III), 1973. (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Planning District 21 (Area III), 1972-1973. (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - General correspondence, 1972-1982. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Consultive Regions - Statistics, 1970-1973. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Slides - Administration, Area Consultants, undated. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Slides - Henrico County Outreach Program, undated. (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Slides - Institutional Consultant, Central State Hospital (Petersburg), undated. (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Slides - Institutional Consultant, Piedmont State Hospital (Burkeville), undated. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Slides - Institutional Consultant, State Penitentiary (Richmond), undated. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Slides - Institutional Consultant, Talking Book Library, undated. (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Brown, Donna (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1978. (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Donna (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1977. (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Brown, Donna (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1976. (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Donna (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1975. (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Brown, Donna (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1974. (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Donna (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1973. (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Chamberlain, William (Public Library Consultant - Area III), 1976. (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Chamberlain, William (Public Library Consultant - Area III), 1975. (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Chamberlain, William (Public Library Consultant - Area III), 1974. (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Chamberlain, William (Public Library Consultant - Area III), 1973. (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Chamberlain, William (Public Library Consultant - Area III), 1972. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Coats, Reed (Institutional Consultant), 1974. (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Garver, Elizabeth (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1973. (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Garver, Elizabeth (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1972 July-Dec. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Garver, Elizabeth (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1972 Jan-June. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Garver, Elizabeth (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1971. (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Garver, Elizabeth (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1970. (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Heath, Jean (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1980. (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Heath, Jean (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1979. (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Heath, Jean (Public Library Consultant - Area I), 1978. (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1982-1984. (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1980-1982. (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1978-1979. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1976-1977. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1975. (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1974. (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1973. (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1972. (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - McLay, Hannah (Public Library Consultant - Area II), 1971. (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Thiele, Barbara (Public Library Consultant), 1979-1981. (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1971-81. (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1981. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1980. (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1979. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1978. (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1977. (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1976. (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1975. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1974. (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1972 May-Dec. (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1972 Jan-Apr. (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1971 July-Dec. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1971 Jan-June. (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Raymond (Public Library Consultant - Area IV), 1970-1971. (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Subject files, 1928-1989.
    This sub-series consists of 29 boxes and is arranged alphabetically.
    - American Library Association (ALA), 1976-1979. (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 1974-1975. (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 1972-1973. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 1970-1971. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 1965-1969. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - American Library Association (ALA) - Conference, 1937. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - American Library Association (ALA) - Conference (Richmond, Va.), 1936. (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - American Library Association (ALA) - Conference (Richmond, Va.), 1936. (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - American Library Association (ALA) - Conference (Richmond, Va.), 1936. (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - American Library Association (ALA) - State and National Planning Committee, 1949-1952. (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - American Library Association (ALA) - State and National Planning Committee, 1946-1948. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Annual reports, 1922-1937. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Annual reports, 1936-1950. (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Annual reports, 1950-1956. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Annual reports, 1944-1953. (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Annual reports, 1956-1969. (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Annual reports, 1970-1978. (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Applications - Demonstration Library, 1956. (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Applications - Demonstration Library, 1957-1961. (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Applications - Negro librarians, 1952-1953. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Applications withdrawn (A-B), 1946-1955. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Applications withdrawn (C-D), 1946-1955. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Applications withdrawn (E-G), 1946-1957. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Applications withdrawn (H-K), 1946-1957. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Applications withdrawn (L-M), 1947-1955. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Applictions withdrawn (N-R), 1948-1957. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Applications withdrawn (S), 1948-1954. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Applications withdrawn (T-Z), 1947-1954. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Applications retired, 1946-1950. (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Audio-Visual Institute, 1967. (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Basic Reference List - Bibliographies of approved books, 1967-1977. (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Bookmobile plans, 1959-1968. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Bookmobiles, 1956-1974. (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Bookmobiles, 1960-1961. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Bookmobiles, 1960-1970. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Book of the Month Club awards, 1960-1964. (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Certification of Expenditures, 1972-1973. (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Certification of Expenditures, 1972-1973. (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Certification of Expenditures, 1972-1973. (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Certification of Expenditures, 1972-1973. (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Certification of Expenditures, 1972-1973. (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Checklist - Certification letters, 1972-1973. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Certification of librarians, 1937-1947. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Community Analysis Institute, 1977. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Community Analysis Institute, 1977. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Community Analysis Institute - Evaluations, 1977. (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Community Analysis Institute - Handouts, 1977. (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Community Analysis Institute - Hyatt House, 1977. (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Demonstration libraries, 1953. (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Extention Division - Articles, etc., 1948-1961. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Extension Division - Miscellaneous, 1969-1970. (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Federal aid, 1957-1961. (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Federal aid, 1960-1971. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1987. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1986. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1985. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1984. (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1983. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1982. (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1981. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1980. (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1979. (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1978. (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1977. (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1976. (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1975. (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1974. (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1973. (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1972. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Form letters and mailings, 1962-1971. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service, 1961. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service, 1962. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service, 1971. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service, 1971. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service, 1971. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Correspondence, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Correspondence, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Correspondence, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Correspondence, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Correspondence, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Correspondence (Gov. Holton to General Assembly), 1971. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Expenditures, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Invitees, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Invitees, 1971. (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Invitees suggested by the Virginia House and Senate, 1971. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Local arrangements, 1971. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Memos, 1971. (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Photographs, 1971. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Press clippings, 1971. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Speakers, 1971. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (A), 1971. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (C-D), 1971. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (H-I), 1971. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (L-M), 1971. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (N), 1971. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (O), 1971. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (P-V), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Other state conferences (Texas), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Virginia, 1971. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (General), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Abingdon), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Charlottesvilled), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Chesterfield), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Courtland), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Danville), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Dublin), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Falls Church), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Farmville), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Fishersville), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Fredericksburg), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Glenns), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Hampton), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Heathsville), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Lynchburg), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Richlands), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Salem), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Virginia Beach), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Winchester), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Wise), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Governor's Conference on Public Library Service - Follow-up meetings (Wytheville), 1971. (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Library Services and Construction Act - Correspondence (E.D. Mullen), 1958-1961. (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Library Services and Construction Act - Correspondence (E.D. Mullen), 1962-1964. (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Library Services and Construction Act - Correspondence (E.D. Mullen), 1965-1968. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Libraries - Proposed (Farmville Area), 1947-1952. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Libraries - Proposed (Gloucester, Mathews, Middlesex, King and Queen), 1948-1958. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Libraries - Proposed (Northern Neck), 1941-1948. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Libraries - Proposed (Northern Neck), 1949-1961. (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Libraries - Proposed (Petersburg Area), 1941. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Library Outreach Cooperative, 1978-1980. (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Library Services - Bookmobiles, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Library Services - Children, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Library Services - Delivery, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Library Services - Hospitals, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Library Services - Library of Congress, 1978-1980. (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Library Services - Institutions, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Library Services - Miscellaneous, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Library Services - Outreach, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Library Services - Preschool, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Library Services - Prisons, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Library Services - Senior Citizens, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Library Services - Shut-ins, 1979. (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Long-range Planning, 1970-1975. (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda (Randolph Church), 1958-1960. (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda (Randolph Church), 1961-1965. (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda (Randolph Church), 1966-1968. (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda (Miscellaneous), 1964-1969. (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda (Public Libraries), 1965-1969. (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Washington Library Council, 1985. (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Mimeographed letters and forms, 1947-1949. (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Mimeographed letters and forms, 1950-1952. (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Mimeographed letters and forms, 1953-1955. (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Mimeographed letters and forms, 1956-1964. (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Monthly statistics, 1948-1954. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - National Association of State Libraries, 1936-1940. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - National Library Week, 1958-1959. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - National Library Week, 1960-1961. (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - National Library Week, 1962. (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - National Library Week, 1963-1967. (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Negro librarians, 1947. (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Ogden, Jess and Jean, 1946-1954. (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Old Dominion Foundation, 1953-1956. (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Parent Teacher Association, 1951-1964. (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Peabody College, 1980-1981. (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1974. (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1975. (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1976. (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Piedmonst Mailbox Library, 1977. (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library - Catalogs, undated. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library - Catalogs, undated. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Position descriptions and pay plans, 1950. (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Positions vacant, 1951-1957. (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Letters of acceptance, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Letters of invitation, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Letters of regret, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Letters of regret, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Letters to people who attended, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Letters to people who did not attend, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Letters to the Governor, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Mailing lists, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Miscellaneous, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Present status, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Press releases, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Public Library Development meetings - Programs, 1973. (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Public Library Institute, 1954. (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Public Library Institute, 1955. (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Public Library Institute Committee on Job Analysis and Pay Plans Survey, 1950. (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Public Library Institute Committee on Job Analysis and Pay Plans Survey, 1950. (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Public Library Institute Committee on Job Analysis and Pay Plans Survey, 1950. (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Public Library Institute Committee on Job Analysis and Pay Plans Survey, 1950. (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Public Library Demonstration Bill, 1946-1951. (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Regional Planning Committee, 1959. (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Rosenwald Fund, 1929-1941. (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Salary scales, 1956-1959. (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Salary scales, 1960-1963. (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Salary scales, 1964-1966. (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Salary scales, 1967-1970. (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Salary scales, 1971-1972. (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Salary scales, 1972-1974. (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Salary scales, 1975-1976. (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Salary scales, 1976-1979. (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Scholarship materials, 1957-1973. (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Slemp Foundation, 1943-1951. (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Smoky Bear Vacation Reading Club, 1958-1959. (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Snyder, Margaret, 1947-1950. (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Southeastern Library Association, 1946-1951. (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Southeastern Library Association, 1954-1966. (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Southeastern Library Association - Southeastern Librarian, 1950-1963. (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Southeastern Library Association - Committees, 1951-1969. (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Southeastern Library Association - Solar Energy Project, 1978. (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - State aid, 1941-1946. (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - State aid, 1947-1948. (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - State aid, 1942-1953. (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - State aid, 1952. (Box 112, Folder 7)